https://www.armaturecoil.com/privacy-policy/

THE ORIGINAL BURN OFF OVENS
"I have owned a number of ovens over the years, including a few of your competitors. The ACE system is More Durable And Dependable...great performance...more energy efficient and much better temperature control"
Mike Stewart, Former International President of EASA
"You make a really good oven. It is very durable. We had a few ovens that we did No Maintenance On For 10 Years and they still run well. Very rugged and dependable."
Brian Charnigo, Techneglas. Owns 12 ACE Ovens
"Your oven system works great! We use it to burn oils off parts before we weld. We just purchased our second oven because we were so pleased with the first one. Very happy with the service level after the sale."
Rick Walden, Prestolite
"Really good equipment. We Have Both Coil Winding Equipment and Ovens and are really pleased with both. Your inside support is excellent."
Dave Lathrop, Gary Electric
"Uses 8-10 times per month to clean wood finishes from hooks. No problems. "We recommended the oven to several other La-Z-Boy plants"
Roger Woodworth
"We are very happy with the ACE system. We have used other brands and found the ACE Oven To Be Superior in performance and durability"
Dan Breazedale, American Brake and Clutch Who Owns 4 ACE Ovens
"Works like a charm. We even strip plastic from our steel parts. This is our second oven. The first one lasted over 20 years."
Eddie King, Plastic Industries
"The oven is working very well"
Bruce Colbert, Ridge Tool Company (China)
"Great Performance of Hybrid Radiant Tube Oven"
Mr. Dan Parson (EASA Travelling Chief) of AC Electric, Bangor
Read More
Privacy Policy - Armature Coil Equipment
The Type of Information We Collect on the Website
User Submitted Information:
This is personally identifiable information or personal information that is voluntarily submitted by a user on the website. Some examples of this information include an email address, name, and phone number, mailing address, credit card or other billing information.
Cookies Information:
When you use the website, we may send cookies to your device. Cookies are basically small files featuring a string of alphanumeric characters. On this website, we use two types of cookies— persistent cookies and session cookies. A session cookie is temporarily available until you use the browser, however, a persistent cookie is retained even after you close the browser. The persistent cookie is used by your browser on your next visit to the website. Please see the “Help” file on your browser to learn how to manage the cookie settings. Please note that if you choose not to accept the cookies or delete them, then you may not be able to utilize a few features of this website to the fullest.
Automatically Collected Information: When you visit the Armature Coil website, some information is automatically collected, and are not stored as personal information. Our server collects the following information:
The name of your Internet service provider
Your IP address
The website from which you visited us
Use of Information Collected by Us
We may use the information provided by you in the following ways:
The personally identifiable information submitted by you on the forms on our website to market you to your preferences— specified by you during the submission. We perform various types of marketing— business-to-business direct marketing and promotional information related to our products or services.
The personal information shared by you will be utilized to fulfill your requests such as responding to your queries, providing updates, newsletters, and so on. We may use the information to contact you regarding the upgraded services, or provide you product updates, white papers, or inform you about market research opportunities, and any other important information related to our business.
We may use the automatically collected information and cookies information in the following ways:To personalize user experience: We will remember your information, which means you don’t have to enter it again when you visit the website anytime.
To provide customized information: We will use the information to provide you with special information regarding customized advertisements, information, and content.
To analyze the effectiveness of some services: We utilize third-party services for marketing. So, we may use the automatically-captured information to analyze the effectiveness of marketing.
To monitor site usage: We use the information to monitor and gain insights into metrics such as the number of pages viewed, total number of visitors to the website, the most viewed pages on the website, and so on.
To monitor your responses: The cookies and automatically-collected information may be used to track your submissions, entries, and status in services, activities, or promotions on the website.
Information Disclosure
Except for the following cases, we do not disclose the information to any third party without your consent.
We collaborate with various third-party service providers for website designing, application development, maintenance, hosting, and other web-related services. These parties have partial access to your information, and they may utilize it for providing the services to you on our behalf. We only share the information that is necessary to perform certain functions on our behalf. We also have confidentiality agreements with them to prohibit the unauthorized use of the information shared.
We may share certain aggregated, automatically collected, or non-personally identifiable information with third parties for purposes, including:
Adherence to reporting obligations
To assist the third-parties for marketing or business purposes
To assist the third parties in understanding our users’ habits and interests for certain content, programs, advertisements, services, promotions, and so on.
We may disclose the personal information shared by you, if required by the law in the belief that it is necessary to comply with federal or state laws, or in response to a government, judicial subpoena, a warrant, a court order, or to cooperate with governmental agencies or other law enforcement institutions.
We reserve the right to share your information when we believe it is necessary to
Protect ourselves from liability
Protect us and our business or others from abusive, fraudulent, or unlawful uses or activities
Defend our business against any allegations or third-party claims
Protect the integrity or security of a service, a piece of equipment, or any facilities used to make the service available
Protect our legal rights or property or the rights and property of others
Your Choices
Client/Prospect Opt-Out: We maintain several contact lists to communicate with our long-term prospects and regular clients. All the emails sent to the prospects or regular clients have an opportunity to unsubscribe or opt-out of future messages. Also, you may contact us at sheran@armaturecoil.com requesting to be removed from the future email messages.
Retention of Your Personal Information:
At Armature Coil, we retain information, as long as you have an account with us or wish to avail our services or products. We may edit or delete the account on your request. If you wish to edit any personal information shared with us, please contact us on our phone number mentioned below. Please note that any information update may take time to reflect on our active databases. We may retain all the information submitted by you for archiving, backups, analytics monitoring, prevention of abuse and fraud, in compliance with legal obligations, or any other reason to do so.
Links to Third-Party Sites
Armature Coil may contain links to third-party websites. Any information that you may submit on any third-party website will be governed by their terms and policies. We are not responsible for the content security or privacy of the information entered by you on a third-party website. This stands true even if you are accessing their website through armaturecoil.com. So, we encourage you to read the content security and privacy policies of the third party websites before sharing your information with them.
Children’s Privacy Rights
The Armature Coil website is intended for adults. We do not encourage account creation by children under 13 years of age. The use of our website requires the creation of the account by an adult, who will be responsible for all activities under the account. All data collected on the account is assumed to be related to an adult. Our services are not directed to children, so we may not knowingly collect any information from the children using our website. If it comes to our notice that any personally identifiable information shared on the website is entered by a child without verifiable parental consent, then we may delete the information. If you are a guardian or a parent who has noticed your child has creating an account on our website, you may alert us through an email or contact us on the phone number mentioned, and request us to delete the details.
Data Security
We use various technical, managerial, and physical safeguards to protect the security and integrity of your identifiable information. However, we cannot warrant the security of the information you submitted on the website, because you do so at your own discretion and risk. We also do not guarantee that despite all the technology-driven and managerial precautions, your information will never be disclosed, accessed, destroyed, or altered by anyone.
If we notice the breach of security systems, we may notify you the same electronically, so that you can easily take any protective steps. Depending on the state, you also have a legal right to receive the hardcopy of the notice of a security breach on the website.
Privacy and Security Settings
At Armature Coil, we allow our prospects and clients privacy, so allow them to adjust their privacy settings according to their preferences. Please be informed that no security measures or privacy settings are impenetrable. We are not responsible for the tampering of security measures or privacy settings on the website. Also, we cannot take responsibility to control the actions of users with whom you might have already shared or wish to share your information. Although we may have removed your information from the website, still it is cached, and archived. Third-parties associated with our business may have stored or copied the information submitted by you. So, we cannot guarantee that the information provided by you will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.
Consent for Information Sharing - International Visitors
The website is hosted in the United States. We sell industrial ovens within the United States and also ship it to other regions of the world. If you choose to use the website from your country then the laws governing data submission and use may differ from the laws in the United States. So, please note that you are sharing your personal information outside your country to the United States for storage and order or request processing. We may transfer the personal data shared by you from here to the country where you are located in connection with fulfilling your orders or special service requests. In such cases, by sharing your personal information with us, you are consenting to the data collection, processing, and storage in the U.S, as outlined by this privacy policy.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We may update our privacy policy from time to time. So we request you to revisit this page to stay aware of these changes. When we change this policy, we will mention it on the website indicating the date of the revision. If the modifications alter your obligations or rights, we will ensure that you are duly notified of the change. For example, we may send an email to your verified email address, or create a pop-up or utilize any other means of notification that informs you of the change for the first time you access the website after the change. Your continued use of the website after the revision of privacy policy will mean that you have clearly noticed, understood, and agreed to the revisions before continuing on the website.
Contact Us
For any questions, comments, or concerns on this privacy policy, you can contact us using the below-given information:
By Email:sheran@armaturecoil.com
By Phone:800-255-1241
FREE TEST CLEANING
REQUEST FOR QUOTE
